Guide to the Beyond the Pale Records TAM.718
Tamiment Library and Robert F. Wagner Labor Archives
- Marathon Special with Ruchama Marton and Basya Schechter, Part 1 [2000-062], 2000-10-22 (Box 14, Item 718_0498)
- Marathon Special with Rashid Khalidi and Frank London, Part 2 [2000-063], 2000-10-22 (Box 14, Item 718_0499)
- Marathon Special with Frank London and Michel Warschawski, Part 3 [2000-064], 2000-10-22 (Box 14, Item 718_0500)
- Liz Krueger and Roy Goodman on NYS Senate Race; Phyllis Bennis on US/UN Role in Israel/Palestine Conflict [2000-079-z], 2000-10-29 (Box 13, Item 718_0467)
- A: Winona La Dulce, Voice endorses Nader for President, Mideast in Clinton/Lazio race / B: Max Bohmel on Israeli Palestinians, Jews of Morocco with Vivian Mann and Habiba Boumlik [2000-28], 2000 November 5; 2000 November 12 (Box 9, Item 718_0291)
- Winona LaDuke, Green Party VP Candidate; Gore v. Nader; the Middle East in the Clinton/Lazio Race [2000-042], 2000-11-05 (Box 13, Item 718_0478)
- Alice Shalvi [2000-038], 2000-11-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0657)
- Max Bohnel on Israeli Palestinians; Jews of Morocco with Vivian Mann and Habiba Boumlik [2000-041], 2000-11-12 (Box 13, Item 718_0477)
- Segev Khalidi [2000-11], 2000-11-18 (Box 8, Item 718_0274)
- Segev Khalidi [2000-12], 2000-11-18 (Box 8, Item 718_0275)
- A: Jeremy Burton on Election 2000, Dalia Kandiyoti interviews Ammiel Alcalay / B: Rhoda Berenson on Lori Berenson, Karah Newton and Anna Cheung on DKNY protest, Alicia Svigals on "Women in Klezmer and Yiddish Music" [2000-27], 2000 November 19; 2000 November 26 (Box 9, Item 718_0290)
- Jeremy Burton on Election 2000; Dalia Kandiyoti Interviews Ammiel Alcalay [2000-086-z], 2000-11-19 (Box 13, Item 718_0473)
- Rhoda Berenson; DKNY Campaign; Alicia Svigals on Women in Klezmer and Yiddish Music [2000-087-z], 2000-11-26 (Box 13, Item 718_0474)
- A: Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev in conversation / B: Sephardic Film Festival, United Federation of Teachers contract, JFREJ and NYC coalition politics [2000-22], 2000 December 3; 2000 December 10 (Box 9, Item 718_0285)
- Sephardic Film Festival; United Federation of Teachers (UFT) Contract Negotiations; JFREJ and NYC Coalition Politics [2000-071], 2000-12-03 (Box 14, Item 718_0507)
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev [2000-008], 2000-12-10 (Box 8, Item 718_0271)
- Segev/Khalidi [2000-78], 2000-12-10 (Box 9, Item 718_0301)
- Rashid Khalidi and Tom Segev in Public Conversation at Congregation B'nai Jeshurun [2000-065], 2000-12-10 (Box 14, Item 718_0501)
- A: Daniel Singer tribute, Laura Whitehorn on Alan Berkman, Geula Jeffet Atar and Victor Atar on "Duel Solitudes" at LaMama, Harriet Tanzman int. Robbie Meeropol on death penalty Exhibition at the Puffin Room / B: Tamara Cohen on Hanukkah, Matt McDonald on the Jewish Music Festival at the Knitting Factory, Leslie Cagan on WBAI and Pacifica [2000-23], 2000 December 17; 2000 December 24 (Box 9, Item 718_0286)
- Tribute to Daniel Singer; Laura Whitehorn on Alan Berkman; Geula and Victor Attar on Dual Solitudes; Robert Meeropol Interview [2000-074], 2000-12-17 (Box 14, Item 718_0510)
- Hanukkah Show with Tamara Cohen, Matt McDonald, and Leslie Cagan [2000-073], 2000-12-24 (Box 14, Item 718_0509)
- Ocean Hill-Brownsville, Thirty Years Later [2000-17], 2000-12-26 (Box 8, Item 718_0280)
- 30 Years After Ocean Hill, Reel 1 [1998-054], 2000-12-26; cuid2612 (Box 34, Item 718_1002, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_610)
  30 Years after Oceanhill-Brownsville
  Original Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 67 min.
- 30 Years After Ocean Hill, Reel 2 [1998-053], 2000-12-26; cuid2611 (Box 34, Item 718_1001, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_609)
  30 Years after Ocean Hill
  Original Format: 1/4" Open Reel Audio, Duration: 37 min.
- A: Rabab Abdelhadi on Israel/Palestine conflict; Jewish Film Festival with Jim Hoberman and Aviva Weintraub / B: Excerpt from The Moment of the Wandering Jew; Ben Shahn photo Exhibition; Nan Rubin and Lynn Gumbert of NYU Grey Gallery; Jennifer Bleyer with Susan Douglas and Hyang Lee [2001-061], 2000 December 31; 2001 January 1 (Box 9, Item 718_0310)
- Ben Shahn Photo Exhibition; Lower East Side Housing; Excerpt from The Moments of the Wandering Jew [2000-069], 2000-12-31 (Box 14, Item 718_0505)
- Jewish Film Festival [2001-0105] (Box 21, Item 718_0951)
- The Flashpoints, Collection of Poems by Aurora Levins-Morales [2015-007], circa 2001 (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_604)
- Rabbi Arthur Waskow: Sukkot Reflections on WTC Attacks [2001-0104] (Box 21, Item 718_0950)
- Israel: Tel Aviv Protests, Netivot, Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark in Tel Aviv, Hotline for Migrant Workers, Part 1, 2001 January - February (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_294)
- Israel: Dalit Baum Who Profits?, Jaffa Housing Crisis, Weitzman School, Part 2, 2001 January - February (Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_295)
- Theater and Social Change [2001-0181], 2001-01-02 (Box 10, Item 718_0328)
- Aviva Weintraub on Jewish Film Festival; Kathleen Blee on Inside Organized Racism [2001-0142], 2001-01-06 (Box 15, Item 718_0550)
- Rabab Abdulhadi on Middle East; Jim Hoberman and Aviva Weintraub on Jewish Film Festival [2001-0114], 2001-01-07 (Box 14, Item 718_0522)
- A: Jerrold Nadler on the new congress; Robert Jackson on Campaign for Fiscal Equity's public education lawsuit / B: Elliot Mincberg on John Ashcroft, Mosco Boucault on Terrorists in Retirement; Jennifer Bleyer on J20 protest at Bush's inaugural [2001-0178], 2001 September 14; 2001 September 21 (Box 10, Item 718_0325)
- Rep. Jerrold Nadler on New Congress; Robert Jackson on Landmark Court Decision [2001-0118], 2001-01-14 (Box 14, Item 718_0526)
- Mosco Boucault on Terrorists in Retirement; Elliot Mincberg on John Ashcroft; Jennifer Bleyer on J20 Protest [2001-0115], 2001-01-21 (Box 14, Item 718_0523)
- A: Jerome Segal, Michel Warschawski, Edison and NYC Schools / B: Alan Levine on Chavas, Joe Conn on Bush's faith initiative, hannah Saffron on Israeli elections [2001-058], 2001 January 28; 2001 February 4 (Box 9, Item 718_0307)
- Jerome Segal on Bush and Middle East; Michel Warschawski on Upcoming Elections; Andy Stettner and Sandra Rivers on Edison School Takeover of 5 Failing Schools (Partial) [2001-0116], 2001-01-28 (Box 14, Item 718_0524)
- Alice Kessler-Harris Interview on Anzia Yezierska, author of Bread Givers and "The Open Cage" [2001-0206], 2001-02-02 (Box 22, Item 718_0955)
- Charas Court Battle; Bush's Faith Initiative; Current Israeli Politics [2001-0117], 2001-02-04 (Box 14, Item 718_0525)
- A: Richard Cohen, The Avengers; Gila Svirsky on Sharon, Israeli left / B: Critical Resistance conference: Jennifer Bleyer, Kate Rhee, Shayna; Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on Pacifica Meeting; Mary Lowenthal Felstiner on Charlotte Salomon's Book Life? or Theatre? [2001-0174], 2001 February 11; 2001 March 4 (Box 10, Item 718_0321)
- Rich Cohen on The Avengers; Gila Svirsky on Ariel Sharon and the Israeli Left [2001-0132], 2001-02-11 (Box 15, Item 718_0540)
- Marathon 2 hour [2001-0173], 2001-02-18 (Box 10, Item 718_0320)
- Marathon Special: Phyllis Bennis on Iraqi Sanctions; Michel Warschawski on Israel/Palestine; Naomi Klein on No Logo [2001-0129], 2001-02-18 (Box 15, Item 718_0537)
- Critical Resistance Conference; Pacifica Board Meeting; Mary Lowenthal Felstiner on To Paint Her Life: Charlotte Salomon [2001-0131], 2001-03-04 (Box 15, Item 718_0539)
- Mary Lowenthal Felstiner Interview with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz on Charlotte Salomon Biography, To Paint Her Life, 2001-03-04 (Box 22, Item 718_0952)
- A: Abe Beam's legacy with Chris McNickle To Be Mayor of New York; The Marc Rich pardon with Rachel Donadio and Rabbi Mordechai Liebling / B: Bob Ganji on "Drop the Rock" campaign; Ella Shohat, Inderpal Grewal, and Caren Kaplan on Talking Visions: Multicultural Feminism in a Transnational Age [2001-0172], 2001 March 11; 2001 March 18 (Box 10, Item 718_0319)
- Abe Beam's Legacy; Marc Rich Pardon [2001-0112], 2001-03-11 (Box 14, Item 718_0520)
- Hasia Diner on Women, Culture, and Food [2001-0204], 2001-03-13 (Box 22, Item 718_0953)
- Rockefeller Drug Law Repeal; Multicultural Feminism [2001-0111], 2001-03-18 (Box 14, Item 718_0519)
- A: Sam Friedman in Conversation with Jeremy Burton and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Hasia Diner on Jewish Women and Food / B: Confederacy Supporters in the Bush Administration; Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska [2001-059], 2001-03-25; 2001-04-01; cuid2617 (Box 9, Item 718_0308, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_615)
  Sam Freedman author of Jew vs. Jew: The Struggle for the Soul of American Jewry, with Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz and Jeremy Burton; Nan Rubin interviews Hasia Diner on Jewish women and food. Chip Berlet, Political Research Associates, on pro-Confederacy sentiments in the Bush administration, Robert Rosen, author of The Jewish Confederates (University of South Carolina Press), co-host Nan Rubin, Harriet Tanzman interviews Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska, author of The Bread Giver.
- Sam Friedman on Jew v. Jew; Hasia Diner on Jewish Women and Food [2001-0149], 2001-03-25 (Box 15, Item 718_0557)
- Jews and the Confederacy: Chip Berlet on Pro-Confederacy Sentiments in the Bush Administration and Robert Rosen on The Jewish Confederates; Alice Kessler-Harris Interview on Anzia Yezierska [2001-0122], 2001-04-01; cuid2608 (Box 14, Item 718_0530, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_607)
  Chip Berlet, Political Research Associates, on pro-Confederacy sentiments in the Bush administration, Robert Rosen, author of The Jewish Confederates (University of South Carolina Press), co-host Nan Rubin, Harriet Tanzman interviews Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska, author of The Bread Giver.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration: 64 min.
- A: Jonathan Rosen The Talmud and the Internet; Sandra Rivers and Sarah Eisenstein on The Fight against Edison [2001-0175], 2001 April 8; 2001 April 15 (Box 10, Item 718_0322)
- Jonathan Rosen on The Talmud and the Internet; the Edison School Vote with Sara Eisenstein and Sandra Rivers [2001-0120], 2001-04-08 (Box 14, Item 718_0528)
- A: Sam Friedman in conversation with Jeremy burton and Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Hasia Diner on Jewish women and food / B: Confederacy Supporters in the Bush Administration, Alice Kessler Harris on Anzia Yezierska [2001-059], 2001-04-15 (Box 14, Item 718_0529)
- A: Gila Svirsky, Kevin Feinberg, Marc Cooper on L.A. Mayoral Race / B: Ilan Stavans on Latino-Jewish identity; Donna Nevels and Amy Velez; Jeremy Burton on Jewish community relation to Latino community [2001-0183], 2001 April 22; 2001 April 29 (Box 10, Item 718_0330)
- Gila Svirsky; Kevin Feinberg on "Facing History" Holocaust Education; Marc Cooper on L.A. Mayoral Elections [2001-0123], 2001-04-22 (Box 14, Item 718_0531)
- Ilan Stavans, Amy Velez, Donna Nevel, and Jeremy Burton on Latin/Jewish Identity and Latino-Jewish Relations [2001-0119], 2001-04-29 (Box 14, Item 718_0527)
- Crystal Quilt, Disk 1 [2001-0194], 2001-04-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0664)
- Crystal Quilt with Sherry Gorelick, Esther Lederman, and Tamar Katriel, Disk 2 [2001-0191], 2001-04-29 (Box 18, Item 718_0665)
- Ilan Stavans on Latino/Jewish Identity [2001-0100], 2001-04-29 (Box 21, Item 718_0946)
- Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference: Jeff Halper (Tracks 2-3), Rela Mazali (Track 4), and Irena Klepfisz (Track 1) [2001-0195], 2001-05-04-2001-05-06 (Box 18, Item 718_0668)
- Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference (Continued): Rela Mazali and Ali Abunimah [2001-0196], 2001-05-05 (Box 18, Item 718_0669)
- Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark and Marsha Triedman on Chicago Jewish Peace Conference; Lois Cronholm and Leon Botstein on the Center for Jewish History; Mellish on Joey Ramone [2001-056], 2001-05-06 (Box 9, Item 718_0305)
- Lower East Side 5 [2001-0182], 2001-05-06 (Box 10, Item 718_0329)
- Jewish Peace Conference; Center for Jewish History; Joey Ramone Tribute [2001-0108], 2001-05-06 (Box 14, Item 718_0516)
- A: Karen Wheeler on Horowitz Ad, Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum and Jeremy Burton, Amos on slavery reparations, Lee Cokorinos on sanctity of human life conference / B: Gila Svirsky on June 8 Women in Black vigils, Judith Sloan and Warren Lehrer on multi-racial, multi-ethnic Queens [2001-055], 2001 May 13; 2001 June 1 (Box 9, Item 718_0304)
- Slavery Reparations; The Sanctity of Human Life Conference [2001-0107], 2001-05-13 (Box 14, Item 718_0515)
- Rabbi Sharon Kleinbaum on Reparations [2001-0103], 2001-05-13 (Box 21, Item 718_0949)
- Allen Ginsberg Special, 2001-06-03 (Box 9, Item 718_0303)
- Allen Ginsberg Special with Co-host Janet Coleman, Part 2 [2001-0113], 2001-06-03 (Box 14, Item 718_0521)
- Allen Ginsberg Special with Co-host Janet Coleman, Part 1, 2001-06-03 (Box 15, Item 718_0560)
- JFREJ Anti-Arab Racism Workshop, Panel 1 with Sam Husseini, Ella Shohat, and Steven Cohen [2001-0193], 2001-06-03 (Box 18, Item 718_0667)
- Gila Svirsky on June 8th Solidarity Vigils with Women in Black; Warren Lehrer and Judith Sloan on Crossing the BLVD [2001-0140], 2001-06-10 (Box 15, Item 718_0548)
- A: James Tisch, AIDS March, Bruni Burris, Human Rights Watch Film Festival / B: Gay Pride Show [2001-057], 2001 June 17; 2001 June 24 (Box 9, Item 718_0306)
- James Tisch United Jewish Communities (UJC) Chair Nomination; AIDS March; Human Rights Watch Film Festival [2001-0110], 2001-06-17 (Box 14, Item 718_0518)
- Gay Pride Show: Circus Amok with Jennifer Miller and Jenny Romaine and Schmear the Queer Zine with Scott Barry and Brian Kay [2001-0109], 2001-06-24 (Box 14, Item 718_0517)
- A: Marc Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Kagan on Pacifica / B: Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde: The Unsettling Story of Dolly Wilde, Oscar's Unusual Niece; Chip Berlet on the Protocols of the Elders of Zion and Rule by Secrecy [2001-0170], 2001 July 1; 2001 July 8 (Box 10, Item 718_0317)
- Mark Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Busch Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica/BAI [2001-0184], 2001-07-01 (Box 10, Item 718_0331)
- Mark Berenson on Lori Berenson; Doris Boskey on Gidone Busch; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0147], 2001-07-01 (Box 15, Item 718_0555)
- Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde; Chip Berlet on Protocols of the Elders of Zion and Rule by Secrecy [2001-0145], 2001-07-08 (Box 15, Item 718_0553)
- Joan Schenkar on Truly Wilde [2001-0102], 2001-07-08 (Box 21, Item 718_0948)
- A: Two talks from May 5-6 2001 conference: Jeff Halpern and Rela Mazali / B: Mike Wishnie on Supreme Court decisions on immigration; Chuck Zlatkin and Ellis Henican on efforts to save WEVD [2001-0167], 2001 July 29; 2001 July 15 (Box 9, Item 718_0315)
- Mike Wishnie on Immigration; Chuck Zlatkin and Ellis Henican on WEVD [2001-0144], 2001-07-15 (Box 15, Item 718_0552)
- A: Liz Ritter, District 7 City Council Race; India and Israel with Aniruddha Das, Vijay Prashad, and Shubh Mathur / B: Arkady Kagan on District 47 council race; Eva Kollisch on Girl, in Movement; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0168], 2001 August 5; 2001 July 22 (Box 10, Item 718_0316)
- Arkady Kagan in Brooklyn Council Race; Eva Kollisch on Girl In Movement; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica [2001-0106], 2001-07-22 (Box 14, Item 718_0514)
- Junity Conference [2001-0176], 2001-07-29 (Box 10, Item 718_0323)
- Jeff Halpern and Rela Magala Talks from Jewish Unity for a Just Peace Conference [2001-0146], 2001-07-29 (Box 15, Item 718_0554)
- Liz Ritter on District 7 City Council Race; India and Israel with Aniruddha Das, Shubh Mathur, and Vijay Prashad [2001-0138], 2001-08-05 (Box 15, Item 718_0546)
- Falastin Ismael, Director of Ilan; Maria de Pina, Human Resources Director of I'Lam [2001-0190], 2001-08-08 (Box 18, Item 718_0663)
- Jafar Farah of Mossawa Center [2001-0198], 2001-08-09 (Box 18, Item 718_0671)
- A: Dmitry Salita and Jimmy O.; Candidate interview Bronx Borough President Fernando Ferrer / B: Candidate interview Public Advocate Mark Greene; Grady Turner, curator of "Flophouse: Life on the Bowery" [2001-0208], 2001 August 12; 2001 August 19 (Box 10, Item 718_0332)
- Jewish Boxer, Dmitry Salita; Mayoral Candidate Interview with Bronx Borough President Freddy Ferrer [2001-0139], 2001-08-12 (Box 15, Item 718_0547)
- Orient House Demo [2001-0185], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0658)
- Michel Warschawski (Mikado) [2001-0187], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0660)
- Track 1-2: Michel Warschawski (Mikado); Track 3: Peretz Kidron [2001-0189], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0662)
- Gila Svirsky [2001-0199], 2001-08-14 (Box 18, Item 718_0672)
- Yatta 1 (PHR) [2001-0186], 2001-08-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0659)
- Yatta 2 (PHR) [2001-0197], 2001-08-18 (Box 18, Item 718_0670)
- Mark Green, Mayoral Candidate; Grady Turner on Flophouse: Life on Bowery [2001-0141], 2001-08-19 (Box 15, Item 718_0549)
- Gaza 1 [2001-0200], 2001-08-19 (Box 18, Item 718_0673)
- Gaza 3 [2001-0201], 2001-08-19 (Box 18, Item 718_0674)
- W.B. with Michel Warschawski (Mikado) Check [2001-0188], 2001-08-20 (Box 18, Item 718_0661)
- Jews Who Rock with DJ Melish! [2001-0143], 2001-08-26 (Box 15, Item 718_0551)
- A: Mayra Peters-Quintero and Andy Stettner on Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Oscar Palacios, Richard Greene, Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton / B: Primary Preview with Norm Fruchter, Andy Stettner, Brad Lander, Kathy Goldman; Jonathan Bowles on State Budget Crisis [2001-0171], 2001-09-02; 2001-09-09; cuid2616 (Box 10, Item 718_0318, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_614)
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn. Co-host, Nan Rubin. Mayoral Primary Show on the issues, with Kathy Goldman (CFRC), Andy Stettner (JFREJ), Norman Fruchter (Institute for Education andf Social Policy, NYU), Brad Lander (Fifth Avenue Committee and ANHD); the New York State Budget with Jonathan Bowls, Center for an Urban Future.
- Tuv Taam Labor Dispute; Crown Heights Riots 10 Years [2001-0136], 2001-09-02; cuid2609 (Box 15, Item 718_0544, Box Electronic Records, E-records TW_TAM_718_ER_608)
  Melanie Kaye/Kantrowitz, Jeremy Burton and Richard Green on the 10th anniversary of the Crown Heights riots; Maira Peters-Quintero (PRLDEF attorney), Oscar Palacios (fired worker) and Arieh Lebowitz (Jewish Labor Committee) on the efforts to organize the workers at Tuv Taam in Brooklyn.
  Original Format: DAT, Duration 65 min.
- Primary Elections; State Budget Crunch [2001-0135], 2001-09-09 (Box 15, Item 718_0543)
- Trembling Before G-d [2001-0180], 2001-09-11 (Box 10, Item 718_0327)
- Amira Habiba Brown, Emily Jacir, Ali Abunimah, Nadia Hijab, 2001-09-16 (Box 10, Item 718_0333)
- 1st Anniversary of Intifada with Alisa Solomon, Marilyn Kleinberg Neimark, Phyllis Bennis [2001-0177], 2001 September 24; 2001 September 30 (Box 10, Item 718_0324)
- First Anniversary of Intifada; Phyllis Bennis on U.S. Foreign Policy and Cold War on Recent Events [2001-0134], 2001-09-24 (Box 15, Item 718_0542)
- First Anniversary of Intifada; Phyllis Bennis on WTC/Pentagon Attacks (Rebroadcast) [2001-0127], 2001-09-30 (Box 15, Item 718_0535)
- A: Religious Fundamentalism with Mark Rosenbloom, Chip Berlet and Azar Nafisi / B: Sept 23 Antiwar Tashlich event; Rabbi Arthur Waskow's Sukkot readings on WTC attacks; Merle Vanderhout on immigrant repression post-Sept. 11 [2001-0166], 2001 October 14; 2001 October 7 (Box 9, Item 718_0314)
- Religious Antiwar Responses; Crackdown on Immigrants Post-9/11 [2001-0130], 2001-10-07 (Box 15, Item 718_0538)
- Religious Fundamentalism; Peace Rally Sound [2001-0150], 2001-10-14 (Box 15, Item 718_0558)
- A: Jessica Kowal on Bloomberg; Dr. Zia Mian on Islamic Fundamentalism / B: Yuri Avnery, Gush Shalom; Sandi Simcha DuBowski and Rabbi Steve Greenberg on Trembling Before G-d [2001-0165], 2001 November 11; 2001 October 10 (Box 9, Item 718_0313)
- Uri Avnery and Gush Shalom; Sandi Dubowski and Rabbi Steve Greenberg on Trembling Before G-d [2001-0133], 2001-10-21 (Box 15, Item 718_0541)
- Jael Silliman on Jewish Portraits, Indian Frames, 2001-10-26 (Box 22, Item 718_0956)
- A: Ralph Schoenman on Zionism [2001-0179], 2001-11-01 (Box 10, Item 718_0326)
- Jessica Kowal on Bloomberg; Zia Mian on Islamic Fundamentalism [2001-0148], 2001-11-11 (Box 15, Item 718_0556)
- Yasser Abed Rabbo of the Palestinian Final Status Negotiating Team; Yossi Beilin, Key Architect of the Oslo Accords [2001-0202], 2001-11-11 (Box 18, Item 718_0675)
- A: Jonathan Rosen and Mohammed Fadel on Anti Arab racism; Jeremy Burton and Angelo Falcon on mayoral race / B: D. Perl and A. Stettner on Murdoch/JCRC honor; Jen Bleyer and Bara Sapir; Nan Rubin interviews Robbie Meeropol [2001-060], 2001 November 18; 2002 February 28 (Box 9, Item 718_0309)
- Jonathan Rosen and Mohammed Fadel on Anti-Semitism; NY Mayoral Race with Jeremy Burton and Angelo Falcon [2001-0128], 2001-11-18 (Box 15, Item 718_0536)
- Jonathan Rosen on The Talmud and the Internet [2000-0101], 2001-11-18 (Box 21, Item 718_0947)
- A: David Kertzer The Pope Against the Jews; Avraham Neguise, South Wing to Zion; Matthew Lazar on WTC death of his uncle / B: Michel Warschawski on bombings in Israel; Sheba Skirball on Sephardic Film Festival; Kathy Goldman on rise in food pantry visits [2001-0163], 2001 November 25; 2001 December 2 (Box 9, Item 718_0311)
- David Kertzer on The Pope Against the Jews; Avraham Neguise from South Wing to Zion; Matthew Lasar on the WTC Death of His Uncle [2001-0126], 2001-11-25 (Box 15, Item 718_0534)
- Bombings in Israel and Haifa; 6th Sephardic Film Festival; Rise of Hunger and Homelessness [2001-0125], 2001-12-02 (Box 14, Item 718_0533)
- A: Aviva Weintraub, Jewish Film Festival, Kathleen Blee with MKK / B: Phyllis Bennis on US Policy on Israel/Palestine, Bob Lederer on Pacifica Board, Alisa Solomon latkes for Hanukkah [2001-053], 2002 January 6; 2001 December 9 (Box 9, Item 718_0302)
- Phyllis Bennis on Bush Stance on Israel/Palestine; Bob Lederer on Pacifica Lawsuits; Alisa Solomon with Latke Recipes [2001-0151], 2001-12-09 (Box 15, Item 718_0559)
- A: Tony Kushner, Alisa Solomon, Tom Segev, Jeremy Barton / B: Chip Bendit on radical right response to 9/11; David Kerner on missionaries and cults and Baptist conversion efforts, Ami Eden on Jewish organizations and civil liberties [2001-0164], 2001 December 23; 2001 December 16 (Box 9, Item 718_0312)
- Chip Berlet on the Extreme Right Response to 9/11; David Kerner on Baptist Conversion Efforts; Ami Eden on Jewish Organizations' Lack of Response to Civil Liberties Threats [2001-0124], 2001-12-16 (Box 14, Item 718_0532)
- Kathleen Blee on Inside Organized Racism [2001-0205], 2001-12-19 (Box 22, Item 718_0954)
- Alisa Solomon with Tony Kushner on Homebody/Kabul; Jeremy Burton Interview with Tom Segev on Book One Palestine, Complete [2001-0137], 2001-12-23 (Box 15, Item 718_0545)
- Winter Marathon: Hannah Safran Interview [2002-049], Winter 2002 (Box 22, Item 718_0965)
- Jewish Film Festival Sound: 1) "Brownsville Black and White," 2) "The Travellers," 3) "Strange Fruit" [2002-055], 2002-01-06 (Box 22, Item 718_0971)
- A: Charles Burton - Fresh Demo; Neta Golan on Situation in Ramallah; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica; Rabbi Michael Lerner on Tikkun conference (Partial) / B: Joe Goldman on the crisis in Argentina; Simon Greer on the World Economic Forum [2002-011], 2002 January 20; 2002 January 27 (Box 10, Item 718_0344)
- Charles Barron on Fresh Democracy; Neba Golan on Ramallah Invasion; Leslie Cagan on Pacifica Changes; Michael Lerner on Tikkun Community (Partial) [2002-024], 2002-01-20 (Box 16, Item 718_0584)
- Joe Goldman on the Crisis in Argentina; Simon Greer on the World Economic Forum [2002-022], 2002-01-27 (Box 15, Item 718_0582)